{
    "subject": "resource/Stockdale_High_School_(Bakersfield,_California)",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/isPrimaryTopicOf",
    "object": "http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Stockdale_High_School_(Bakersfield,_California)",
    "human_readable": "The primary topic of Stockdale High School is Stockdale High School (Bakersfield, California).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9491612315177917,
            "question": "What is the primary subject or area of study at Stockdale High School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8290330171585083,
            "question": "What state is Stockdale High School in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8229876160621643,
            "question": "What type of institution is Stockdale High School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8114068508148193,
            "question": "Where is Stockdale High School located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7635547518730164,
            "question": "What is the name of the city where Stockdale High School is located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7319629192352295,
            "question": "Is there anything else distinctive about Stockdale High School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6845259666442871,
            "question": "Is Stockdale High School known for a specific academic focus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.644006609916687,
            "question": "How would you describe the overall environment or culture at Stockdale High School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6375452876091003,
            "question": "Are there any notable alumni from Stockdale High School?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.550209641456604,
            "question": "Does Stockdale High School have any unique programs or offerings?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The primary topic of Stockdale High School is Stockdale High School (Bakersfield, California).",
            "html": "dbpedia_2455_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable alumni from Stockdale High School?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2455_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe the overall environment or culture at Stockdale High School?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2455_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Stockdale High School known for a specific academic focus?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2455_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2455_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2455_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2455_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2455_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2455_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2455_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2455_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2455_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2455_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2455_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to Stockdale High School, including its location in Bakersfield, California. This supports the statement that the primary topic of Stockdale High School is indeed Stockdale High School (Bakersfield, California)."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}